Anooj Vadodkar

A UC Merced undergraduate student pursuing a Bachelors of Science in Computer Science and Engineering, with experience across a variety of languages and engines. Founding officer and current President of the UC Merced Game Development Club, working with the University and other organizations to bring game development knowledge to students.

408-768-6886 anoojrv@gmail.com anooj.xyz https://www.linkedin.com/in/an oojvadodkar/

EDUCATION

University of California At Merced

Bachelors of Science in Computer Science and Engineering August 2018 - Present. GPA: 3.7/4.0

Relevant Coursework: Intro to Object Oriented Programming, Database Systems, Creative And Professional Writing, Technical Writing.

Awards: Dean's Honors List For Semester Of Spring 2019, Fall 2019, and Fall 2021. Chancellor's Honors List for Academic Year 2020-2021.

EXPERIENCE

Student Game Developers Alliance Webmaster

September 2020 - Present

Currently maintaining and updating the website for the Student Game Developers Alliance, or SGDA, namely responsible for making additions and servicing the website to include information about seasonal events such as the SGDA Summit and Game Jam. We participate in weekly scrums to gauge progress, as well as use Airtable for managing deadlines and tasks.

University of California, Merced, Bright Success Center Sophomore Success Intern November 2019 - April 2020

Developed and implemented a data strategy using Excel to analyze Sophomore success and retention at UC Merced, as well as the existing programs on campus that support them. Provided a recommendation list on how to best assist Sophomore students in their university journey.

PROJECTS

Trace Attorney

Self Developed

Developed a visual novel in the Twine engine with a team of five. I worked on overall programming, writing, as well as holding meetings every two days to check on progress and what needed addressing. Submitted to the 2021 SGDA Summer Game Jam, which was one week long.

SKILLS

Database Systems.

Game Development.

Unity and Unreal.

Microsoft Excel.

LANGUAGES

C++ - Advanced

Java - Advanced

SQL - Advanced

Python - Experienced

C# - Experienced

ORGANIZATIONS

UC Merced Game Development Club - President

Student Game Developers Alliance - Webmaster

Association for Computing Machinery - Member

Fencing Club - Vice President